itdarasgah.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy & DMCA | ITDarasgah - Pakistani Urdu Forum for FREE IT Education

We are ITDarasgah - Pakistani Urdu Forum for FREE IT Education ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information please contact us.

## What information we hold about you

The type of data that we collect and process includes:

  * Your name or username.
  * Your email address.
  * Your IP address.

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

  * You register as a member on this site.
  * You fill out our contact form.
  * You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
  * You fill out fields on your profile.

## How your personal information is used

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
  * We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
  * Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

## Other ways we may use your personal information.

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails in your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

## Keeping your data secure

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

## DMCA - Copyright infringement

**ITDarasgah.com** is in compliance with 17 U.S.C. § 512 and in the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”). It is our policy to respond to any infringement notices and take appropriate actions under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) and other applicable intellectual property laws.   
If your copyrighted material has been posted on **ITDarasgah.com** or if hyperlinks to your copyrighted material are returned through our search engine and you want this material removed from this site, then you must provide a written communication that details the information listed in the following section. Kindly be aware that you will be liable for damages (including costs and attorneys’ fees) if you misrepresent information listed on our site that is infringing on your any copyrights. We suggest you that first contact an attorney for legal assistance on this matter.   
**If the following elements/segment must be included in your copyright infringement claim:**

  * Provide an evidence of the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
  * Provide sufficient contact information so that we may contact you. You must also involve a valid email address.
  * You must identify in sufficient detail the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed and including at least one search term under which the material appears in xenforo.pk’s search results.
  * A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

Send the infringement notice via email to this address : Send Mail   
Please allow up to a week for an email response. Kindly note that emailing your complaint to other parties such as our Internet Service Provider will not expedite your request and may result in a delayed response due to the complaint not being filed properly.   
Please fill this form with appropriate complete details with proof… : [Contact us:](https://itdarasgah.com/misc/contact/)

## Cookie policy

Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on this page.

## Rights

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please contact us. If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may contact us to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please contact us if you would like us to remove your personal data.

## Acceptance of this policy

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

## Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.
